<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FOG Network</title>
    <description>»Some description goes here!</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>&#39;Fog&#39; computing harnesses personal devices to speed wireless networks</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;As everyday items from cars to watches increasingly use computers and communications to operate, the demand on networks that connect devices is expected to balloon. In response, engineers are working to harness the devices’ own computing, sensing and storage power to form networks that meet most of the demand. These networks have been dubbed “fog computing,” a name that emphasizes their local, diffuse nature as opposed to more distant “cloud computing.” Now, researchers at Princeton University’s Edge Lab are leading a global effort, with scientists and business leaders at ARM, Cisco, Dell, Intel and Microsoft, to develop the architecture and tools for using these new fog networks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more please follow the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.princeton.edu/main/news/archive/S45/01/91M25/index.xml?section=topstories&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/news/fogconsortium/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/news/fogconsortium/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How Uber Uses your Phone as a Backup Datacenter</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Learn how Uber can failover between datacenters without causing service disruption by restoring trip states from a key value store on driver phones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/0EhTOKcwRok&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/news/uber/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/news/uber/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Finding your Way in the Fog: Towards a Comprehensive Definition of Fog Computing</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For more please follow the &lt;a href=&quot;http://dl.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=2677052&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/researchpaper/news/paper16/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/researchpaper/news/paper16/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Paper16</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For more please follow the &lt;a href=&quot;http://dl.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=2677052&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/paper16/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/paper16/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Report Identifies Fundamental Research Needs for Advancing Internet of Things &amp; Cutting-Edge Innovations</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;A new report, titled, “Rebooting the IT Revolution: A Call to Action,” produced by the Semiconductor Industry Association (SIA) and the Semiconductor Research Corporation (SRC), calls for, “a targeted and coordinated government initiative similar to that which sparked the semiconductor revolution fifty years ago.” Calling this initiative the “National Computing and Insight Technologies Ecosystem initiative,” or N-CITE, the report identifies critical areas where research, particular federally supported research, is needed in order to position the country to enjoy the full benefit of advances in Big Data and the burgeoning “Internet of Things.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more please follow the &lt;a href=&quot;http://cra.org/govaffairs/blog/2015/09/rebooting-it-revolution-report/&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/news/cra/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/news/cra/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>America&#39;s Greatest Makers: Intel is calling on tech innovators to submit their IoT ideas</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;America’s Greatest Makers (working title) is coming to television in 2016. Are you ready to build the next truly amazing device? Bring your big ideas to life with Intel, in collaboration with Mark Burnett, United Artists Media Group, and Turner Broadcasting System. Competitors will vie for a $1 million grand prize.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more please follow the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www-ssl.intel.com/content/www/us/en/wearables/americas-greatest-makers.html&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/news/annoucement/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/news/annoucement/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fog Computing: Bringing Cloud Capabilities Down to Earth</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;When we think of “cloud” we think of a vast collection of compute, network, and storage capabilities that resides somewhere high above us—a massive repository of functionality that can be accessed from anywhere and any device with enough bandwidth to handle the data flow.
With practically unlimited power and scalability, cloud technology has been a key enabler of the Internet. But the Internet of Things (IoT) demands something more. IoT is a broad collection of sensors, cameras, smartphones, computers, and machines—all connected to and communicating with applications, websites, social media, and other devices. To maximize value, much of the data generated by these “things” must be processed and analyzed in real time. For example, sensors and cameras in and around a large retail store may continuously collect data about customer volume and traffic flow. The store can derive some value from all this data by sending it back to the cloud to analyze long-term trends. But the value is multiplied if the system can process the data locally, in real time, and then act on it immediately by sending more cashiers to the check-out line just before a surge in customer traffic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more please follow the &lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.cisco.com/ioe/fog-computing-bringing-cloud-capabilities-down-to-earth&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/blog/blog/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/blog/blog/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>McKinsey report on IoT: The Internet of Things: Mapping the Value Beyond the Hype</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The Internet of Things—sensors and actuators connected by networks to computing systems—has received enormous attention over the past five years. A new McKinsey Global Institute report, The Internet of Things: Mapping the value beyond the hype, attempts to determine exactly how IoT technology can create real economic value.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more please follow the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mckinsey.com/insights/business_technology/the_internet_of_things_the_value_of_digitizing_the_physical_world&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/news/McKinsey-report/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/news/McKinsey-report/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Analytics Evolving to the Edge, Leading Data to Reach 1.6 Zettabytes by 2020, Study Says</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;By the end of the decade, says a recent study by ABI research called “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.abiresearch.com/market-research/product/1021642-edge-analytics-in-iot/&quot;&gt;Edge Analytics in IoT&lt;/a&gt;,” M2M and other IoT-enabled devices will likely have collected more than 1.6 zettabytes (1.6 trillion GB) of data. As a point of caparison, the entire internet was has been estimated to be at somewhere between 4 and 7 trillion GB of data right now. &lt;br /&gt;
“The data originating from connected products and processes follows a certain journey of magnitudes. The yearly volumes that are generated within endpoints are counted in yottabytes, but only a tiny fraction of this vast data mass is actually being captured for storage or further analysis,” said Aapo Markkanen, principal analyst at ABI. “&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more please follow the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fogcomputingworld.com/topics/fog-computing/articles/401431-analytics-evolving-the-edge-leading-data-reach-16.htm&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/news/edge-analytics/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/news/edge-analytics/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cisco Innovation Grand Challenge</title>
        <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;With less than 1% of things in the physical world connected to the Internet, there is an incredible opportunity to connect the unconnected, creating vast opportunities to transform businesses and industries by re-inventing business processes, operational efficiencies and customer service innovations. The Cisco Innovation Grand Challenge will recognize startups, entrepreneurs and developers around the world with the most breakthrough digital technologies, products or business models across a variety of categories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more please follow the &lt;a href=&quot;https://cisco.younoodle.com/#thechallenge&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2015 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/news/cisco-challenge/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/news/cisco-challenge/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
